YeoJin: We came to the restaurant to eat!
The Word Chain game is started while they’re waiting for the food!
HyunJin: 지구 (The Earth)
YeoJin: 구식 (Old-fashioned)
The Word Chain game is started while they’re waiting for the food!
HaSeul: 식사 (Meal)
HeeJin: 사지 (legs and arms)
HyunJin: 지성 (Intellligence)
YeoJin: 성악 (Vocal)
HaSeul: 악어 (Crocodile)
HeeJin: 어장 (Fishery)
HyunJin: 장어 (Eel)
YeoJin: (she messed up) Uh…?
YeoJin’s vocabulary is still limited…
HaSeul: (Practice) Think me as the director. Practice now!
The penalty is acting cute to the director!
YeoJin: The director~~ Please~~~
HyunJin: The director~~ Please~~
HyunJin: Until he says ‘what’s wrong with you?’
'My feet are heavy…'
She is hesitant to approach the director…
'Why do you come here?'
'(YeoJin’s first attempt) The director~~ please~~~'
'(second attempt) The director~~ please~~~'
'(He has good sense) What’s wrong with you?'
Mission success!!
'Thank you, director!!'
She’s going back to her seat without looking back..
The girls are enjoying their meal after finished the game!